ruukki.com 2015-10-17

# Privacy - Ruukki

The protection of your privacy when visiting this website is very important to Ruukki. Please read our Privacy Policy before entering this website. If you do not accept the terms of our Privacy Policy, we expect you to leave this site.

## Using your personal data 

Most of the pages on Ruukki websites are provided mainly for information purposes so that they can be used without you needing to provide personal data. We collect information about how you use Ruukki websites. This information may be may be linked to any personal data Ruukki holds about you. 

We may need to collect personal data through this website for the purpose of providing the information and goods you request and for marketing, sales and business and product development. The use of your personal data is based on your consent. By providing information to Ruukki via this website, you agree to your personal data being used as specified in this Policy. 

Personal data, including names, addresses and telephone numbers which you may provide to Ruukki, will be processed manually and by computer. Ruukki aims to process personal data as efficiently and securely as practicable. In addition, Ruukki seeks to constantly improve the company’s websites to provide a better quality and broader scope of services. 

## Protecting personal data and information security

Ruukki is committed to protecting your privacy and personal data. Ruukki processes your personal data in accordance with the applicable Finnish personal data legislation and this Privacy Policy. Your personal data are not transferred outside Rautaruukki Corporation or its subsidiaries, affiliates or reliable partners.

### Description of data protection file 

**Combined register description file and information form  
**Personal Data Act (523/1999) Sections 10 and 24   
Date of drafting: 15 June 2010 

Controller | 

Name (Business ID)

Rautaruukki Corporation (Business ID: 0113276-9)  
  
---|---  
  
Address

Suolakivenkatu 1, PO Box 138, FI-00811 Helsinki, Finland  
  
Other contact information

+358 20 5911  
  
Controller’s representative | 

 Name

Pia Tanskanen, Vice President, Legal  
  
Address

Rautaruukki Corporation

Suolakivenkatu 1, P.O. Box 138, FI-00811 Helsinki, Finland  
  
Other contact information

Tel. +358 20 59 28813, email: [pia.tanskanen@ruukki.com](mailto:pia.tanskanen@ruukki.com)  
  
Register name |  Rautaruukki Corporation’s product and service customer registers  
Reason for processing personal data | 

The purpose of the register is to process customer data for the: 

  * Maintenance of the www.ruukki.com website and the provision of products, services, recruitment or competitions via websites or other ways. 
  * Development and management of the customer relationship between the service provider and the customer. 
  * Identification of customers and provision of information security. 
  * Management of internal and external responsibilities within Rautaruukki Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates and subcontractors in as much as these relate to provided products and services, recruitment database or internet-competitions arranged by the company. 
  * Provision of information for use by Rautaruukki Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates and subcontractors in direct marketing, data mining and related actions, such as profiling customer data for the above purposes. 

Information content of register | 

Below are some of the categories in which Rautaruukki Corporation collects personal data: 

  * Technical data or the information collected by cookies about the user’s visits to and use of www.ruukki.com sites and related log data that identifies user location, time and use 
  * Information supplied by the customer such as name, street address, telephone number, email address and other contact information which is required, for example, for the supply of goods and services, customer communication and user identification 
  * Customer relationship and contractual information such as customer wishes and order details and information related to other websites and goods and services provided via them 
  * User profiles based on the information above and financial user information related to goods and services 

Regular sources of information | 

  * Cookie information from the clients’ hard drive obtained by Rautaruukki Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates and subcontractors or log data by monitoring use of the website 
  * Information provided by the customer such as general customer and order information 
  * Units within Rautaruukki Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates and subcontractors that provide products, services and value added services (for example logistics services) related to the www.ruukki.com website 

Normal disclosure of information and transfer of information to countries outside the EU or EEA | Information is disclosed and transferred for the purposes defined above to units within Rautaruukki Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates and subcontractors, some of which are located outside the EU and EEA. Also some of the servers used to maintain the www.ruukki.com website may be located outside the EU or EEA.  
Register security | 

A. Manual data

Manual data are kept in locked premises and is available only to authorised persons. 

B. Computer processed data

The website uses technical data protection which aims at ensuring that the information submitted remains unchanged and is available only to authorised persons. Only certain employees of Rautaruukki Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates and subcontractors have a username and password to access the system.  
  
Right to check | 

As a rule, everyone is entitled to check the information held about them on the personal data file. All requests to check the information should be made in writing by letter signed in the hand of the person concerned or by request in person to the controller of the register. Requests to check personal data should be sent to Rautaruukki Corporation at the address provided above.  
  
Correcting information | 

Everyone is entitled to have inaccurate register information about them corrected. Requests to correct information should be made in writing and in sufficient detail. Requests to correct information should be sent to Rautaruukki Corporation at the address provided above.  
  
Download description of data protection file 

Download Register decription file for Ruukki applicant database

## Cookies

From time to time, cookies may be placed on your computer to improve the effectiveness of this website and Ruukki’s services to you. A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. This enables Ruukki to identify you. 

Cookies are commonly used on many websites today. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or if you wish to be notified before they are placed, most web browsers allow you to set the browser to this effect. Please note that if you do not allow cookies, this may affect website or service usability.

## Other provisions

This site may contain links to other websites. Ruukki is not responsible for the contents or security of any other websites. 

Ruukki is continuously developing its websites and may at any time revise the terms of this Privacy Policy by updating it. 

## Contacting Ruukki 

You can correct the accuracy of the personal data we hold about you by contacting Ruukki. At your request, we will correct or delete any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data about you. For more information, please contact Ruukki Legal Affairs (tel +358 20 5911).
